MY DRAMA
traduzione ed encoding by www.mydrama.altervista.org
♪A beautiful place full of smiles♪
♪Where imaginations about you grow wildly♪
♪The winter sun is like your white teeth♪
♪Expecting your visit all day long♪
♪Like the light breeze
and the fragrance of flowers in May and June♪
♪Hesitate to embrace you and my words stumble♪
♪Time passes hurriedly,
leaving a photo of us and sunflowers♪
♪Too flimsy to be scrutinized♪
♪Welcome to my world and explore its beauty♪
♪I can offer you my clumsy gentleness♪
♪Welcome to my lonely island, too♪
♪Only fish and migratory birds have been here♪
♪Maybe I'm too clumsy and evasive♪
♪Tired of troubles,
all I want is to hide you secretly♪
[Hidden Love]
[Adapted from the novel Hidden Love by Zhu Yi]
[Episode 12]
Okay.
Then we'll settle
with this framework.
After that,
we'll quickly address
the issue
of upgrading the visuals.
Sure.
I'll also update
the program schedule
and tell other colleagues.
Thank you for your hard work.
Not at all.
By the way,
I've talked to the building security department
about
strengthening the security here.
If Jiang Ying comes again,
they'll notify you in advance.
Sorry for troubling you.
How is this troubling me?
I just don't get it.
It has been so many years.
Why can't she let go of you
and herself?
So everyone can live in peace.
But it was fortunate this time
that she didn't see
your relative's child.
Or else,
who knows
what she would have done?
Don't dwell on it.
Focus on living
and working.
I know.
I'll get back to work then.
Go ahead.
Until what time did you study last night?
[Don't come]
It was almost 2 AM.
That late?
How was your revision
of the technical overview?
(After this,)
(don't come directly to my office)
(or my house.)
Let me know in advance before coming,
okay?
Can you lend me your notes?
I need to catch up on this subject too.
Okay.
[La-la la-la la-la]
Why is this question so hard?
If you can't solve it, let me take a look.
No.
I must solve it myself.
I need to eat something first
to replenish my energy.
(Is he not planning)
(to call and explain it to me?)
Sang,
do you want to have some?
It's better than yesterday.
Right?
Then, here.
Based on this path below,
it'll be better if you try and test it again.
Again?
Are you trying to slack off?
Okay. Anything you say.
(But it was fortunate this time)
that she didn't see
your relative's child.
Or else,
who knows
what she would have done?
[Brother No. 2]
(When's your exam?)
(Have you bought your plane ticket home
for the holidays?)
[Sang Zhi]
(Next week.)
(I bought a ticket for the 19th.)
(Okay.)
"Okay."
[Flight for the 19th]
[Brother No. 2]
(When will you be free after the exams?)
(Let's have a meal together.)
[Sang Zhi]
(Maybe I won't have time.)
(She might go out with her friends.)
(Forget it.)
(Okay.)
I can't focus at all.
What's wrong?
If I fail the exam this time,
it will be all his fault.
[Weak Chen]
Did you fight with Chen Qiang?
(*Qiang means strong and capable.)
How is he capable, huh?
He's only capable when trying to annoy me.
If you ask me,
he's extremely weak,
Weak Chen!
Stop looking at it.
[10 January, Wednesday]
I've had it.
It's imperative for me
to change my mood immediately.
Wei,
what do you have in mind?
I'm done enduring the bitterness of love.
Only drinking can relieve it.
After the exam is over,
let's go and have fun.
Why don't we go today?
But
I thought your mom
will call you in a little while.
Tomorrow is the exam.
Yeah.
Then,
can we go after the exam?
Sure.
Okay.
I agree.
Everyone is on board.
Now, I'm going to text Jiang Ming
to officially notify everyone
that Weak Chen is not to show up!
You're the person for the job.
(Baby, answer the phone...)
What do you want?
What?
No.
You're so annoying.
Okay, fine.
I'll be down there right away.
Bye.
Ladies, I'll be...
Just go.
I can't stand you.
Wei,
be safe.
Close the door.
I know.
I meant Chen Qiang.
What?
I'll go and take a shower.
Okay.
Sang.
Do you
have something on your mind lately?
You may not
show it.
But
I could feel
you've been feeling down these days.
I think
it started
from the day you delivered
the electronic peephole camera.
Could the relative you sent
the electronic peephole camera to
happen to be your crush?
Well,
something did happen that day.
But it's not considered
anything serious.
Maybe I'm overthinking.
Do you guys still keep in touch?
We do.
But...
I think you treat him
really nicely.
But if he doesn't treat you
well,
you should move on.
He treats me well too.
It's just that...
Wang,
I'm good.
Don't worry about me.
I mean it.
[Chapter 12: Courage. If I could]
-Five.
-Be more accurate.
Six.
Demonstrate it.
It's six.
Which one are you drinking?
I don't get it at all.
Don't ruin my rhythm.
How did your exam go?
Not too bad.
Are you going home tomorrow?
I'm free tomorrow.
So I can send you to the airport.
Don't you have training tomorrow?
You don't have to send me.
Just go for your training.
I can manage.
Okay.
Is your drink nice?
Do you want to try it?
This one has a stronger kick.
If I drink it,
I get drunk quickly.
You're weak.
Try a little.
Don't drink too much.
You don't usually drink alcohol.
Are you feeling dizzy?
Not bad.
Impressive.
Okay, where were we?
It's my turn.
Five.
Six.
I mean five, five, five.
Five, five.
Six.
Do you want
to try adding
that screen space ambient occlusion?
That will make the entire environment
more three-dimensional.
Why didn't I think of that?
I'll go and try adding it.
Go.
Okay.
Thanks, Duan.
[Duan Jiaxu]
(You're going back tomorrow.)
(Have you packed your luggage?)
Thank you, everyone.
That was good.
Where is he going?
Don't tell me he's going to sing.
(I'll send you to the airport.)
Sorry, everyone
for taking some of your time.
I want to dedicate a song
to...
To my friends.
-Okay!
-Good!
♪How do I describe your face?♪
♪Cute with a hint of shyness♪
♪I really want to have♪
♪A little bit of something with you♪
♪Can I call you this?♪
♪Standing like a fool downstairs at your place♪
♪Dialing the phone♪
♪Looking at the cooling egg tart♪
I didn't expect
Jiang Ming to be good at singing.
Besides...
Look.
Jiang Ming looks handsome
like this, right?
Am I right?
Right?
Of course, he's not as handsome as you.
♪Since the day I met you♪
♪I've fallen in love with you♪
I'm going to the washroom.
Do you want me to accompany you?
♪They're all about you♪
She's had too much to drink.
♪Watching the ebb and flow
of the ocean's surface♪
♪It reminds me of you♪
♪Carefully♪
♪I store you in my mind♪
♪A repeating melody♪
Hello?
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
Where are you?
I'm at the bar.
With whom?
My classmates.
Did you drink?
Just a little.
What's the name of the bar?
Qinghong Music
2002 Music Bar.
Okay.
Wait inside for a while.
I'm coming over now.
Why are you coming?
To catch a drunkard.
Hello?
You won't let me go and see you.
But you want to come and see me.
You're so weird.
Thank you.
I have to go back now.
Are you going back now?
How can we not worry if you go back like this?
Did you drink a lot?
I'm fine.
My brother is coming to pick me up.
Bye, guys.
Is she going alone?
I'll walk her out then.
-Okay, go.
-Go quickly.
She should be fine, right?
Yes.
Be careful.
It's okay.
Watch your steps.
Slowly.
You don't have to follow me.
You can stay with them.
I didn't drink that much.
I'll be here
waiting for my brother to pick me up.
Are you cold?
You're not wearing thick enough.
I'm not cold.
I'm really not cold.
Sang Zhi.
Actually,
I wanted to dedicate
that song to you.
I...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just want to stay like this for a while.
There's a bench there.
Let me help you walk over there.
It's okay.
You'll feel even worse like this.
I'm really okay.
I'm okay.
Don't touch me.
What are you doing?
Jiaxu.
Get up.
I didn't drink a lot.
I'm fine.
Are you Sang Zhi's brother?
I go to the same university as Sang Zhi.
My name is Jiang Ming.
Nice to meet you.
I'm here now.
So thank you.
Okay.
Then I'll go back inside.
Where are we going?
Who says you can drink at a bar?
I'm an adult.
I'm a grown-up now.
Why can't I visit a bar?
Even so, you can't drink this much.
Why can't I be there
when I'm an adult?
Are you angry?
You said so.
You told me
that when I grow up,
I can do what I want.
But now, I've grown up.
I'm already an adult.
But there are still
many things I can't do.
And maybe I just dare not do them.
Where are you going?
Home.
What's the matter?
I feel sick.
I feel like throwing up.
If you want to throw up, go ahead.
You'll feel better after that.
I can't.
Then let's go
sit over there for a while.
No.
We'll just stay here.
You're squatting in the cold.
You'll feel even worse if you catch a cold.
I just want to stay here for a while.
I don't feel well.
I'll carry you there,
okay?
I...
Be good.
I don't want to move.
Get up.
I'm sorry.
I...
Why are you apologizing?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I feel nauseated.
What's wrong?
Don't be mean to me.
Do you feel like throwing up?
Just do it if you want to.
Don't be mean to me.
I won't.
When have I ever been mean to you?
Can you hold on a little longer?
It's too windy here.
It'd be bad if you catch a cold.
Let's go.
I'll carry you on my back.
What's wrong?
You can't carry me.
Why not?
The doctor said
you've just had surgery.
Over here.
You can't do any heavy lifting
for three months.
Over here.
It's already been three months.
Really?
Then you...
Can you carry me?
Sure.
Stand up and I'll carry you on my back.
Come on.
Get on.
I must be crazy.
♪I wipe off the dust because you're still there♪
You can't carry me.
Well, why not?
I weigh over 45 kilograms.
♪I hide my wish under a band of stars
like a clumsy kid♪
I weigh over 45 kilograms.
The thing is my chest is still flat.
What...
What are you talking about?
I weigh over 45 kilograms.
Wait.
It's really flat.
What do you mean by flat?
You're laughing.
Do you even have it?
Wait.
♪Every inch of the wound is softly veiled
within the halo's radiance♪
I don't have it.
I don't have it either.
Get up first.
I really don't have it.
♪Every night freezes into an eternal day
amidst the fireworks♪
But I hope
you won't be too sad about it.
Things like this
are beyond our control.
Okay...
I won't feel sad.
If I'm not sad,
you must not be sad.
You can't cry.
Stop crying.
♪You unlocked the hidden corners of my heart♪
So,
can I carry you home now?
♪I can no longer hide all those sweet thoughts♪
Be good.
Stop crying.
♪Growing up with you♪
♪I'm just afraid♪
Get on.
♪Losing the fairy tales you promised♪
Stay still.
♪In the flowing universe♪
Stop crying, okay?
♪Our meetings secretly filling the gaps
in the Milky Way♪
Then,
what if
I want to throw up again?
Before you throw up,
give me a heads-up.
I'll try not to sway too much
so you'll feel more comfortable.
Then I'll just do this.
Okay.
I won't feel like throwing up doing this.
Jiaxu.
I have a secret.
A secret
that I've been hiding in my heart.
Do you want to tell me?
Well,
there's...
There's someone
I really like.
But
he just doesn't like me.
Who's that?
I can't tell you.
Not even me?
Yes.
I'm sad.
I'm so sad.
Because
of the person you like?
You really can't tell me
who that is?
Then tell me
what kind of person he is.
Does he treat you well?
You can tell me that much, no?
He's...
What?
I don't how to put it into words.
What do you mean?
He's really nice.
He's also really nice to me.
But he's nice to everyone.
He's just nice to all.
He's like a central air conditioning system.
(*Being nice to many of the opposite gender)
So he made you so heartbroken.
If he's someone like that,
stop liking him.
Can you do that?
Sang Zhi.
So that's the kind of guy you like.
Is it okay if I become like him?
Then I'll only be good to you.
That way, our Sang Zhi
would no longer
be so sad.
Letting someone else take care of you
doesn't put me at ease at all.
If you just keep quiet,
I'll take it as a yes.
My situation has improved.
I've paid all my debts.
I have a pretty great personality.
I'm just
a bit older than you.
When I was 21,
you thought I was old.
Now, rounding it off,
you're almost twenty.
Sang Zhi is a grown-up now.
What am I doing?
(I threw up.)
(I threw up on Jiaxu.)
He
said...
Forget it.
What was there to say
to a drunkard like me?
[Brother No. 2]
(Are you awake?)
(I asked your roommate)
(to wake you up at nine.)
(All the flights at this time)
(are sold out.)
(You can't change your flight.)
(So you have to get up.)
(Or else you won't be able to go back.)
(After you wake up, drink more water.)
(I'll pick you up at ten)
(and take you to the airport.)
Oh, you're up.
You're finally awake, Sang.
Yes.
How are you feeling?
-Slowly.
-Watch your head.
Was the person who sent you back last night
your brother's friend,
your crush whom you mentioned
before?
Is he the one?
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
You said he was handsome,
but you didn't say he was that handsome.
I told you before.
How could I know
he's such good-looking?
Compared to Chen Qiang,
Chen Qiang is truly weak.
He's not a match for him.
Not at all, okay?
Oh.
When he
sent me back here yesterday,
did
he
look upset?
No.
Did he look upset?
Nope.
He looked pretty fine to me.
Upset?
Wait a minute.
Did you do something to him?
Nothing.
What did you do?
Nothing? I don't believe you.
I didn't do anything.
Anyway, you guys
have to watch me.
I must never drink anymore.
If I ever drink,
I'm a dog.
What did you do?
Did you kiss him?
No, I did not. I would never.
Why are you so worked up?
I'm sure you did.
You must have confessed your feelings to him.
Am I right?
Did you confess to him?
If I did confess,
I probably
wouldn't wake up today.
-Then what did you do?
-What did you do to him?
-Tell us.
-Come on.
I did nothing.
She couldn't have vomited, right?
Impossible.
You didn't, right?
Did you throw up?
Did you really
throw up on him?
Well...
I need to pack my things.
I... I have to pack up my stuff.
So,
she did throw up.
She threw up on her crush.
Sang
threw up on your crush.
Why does he insist on taking me to the airport?
How can I face him
after what happened last night?
Good morning, Jiaxu.
Morning.
Let me help you with your luggage.
Sang Zhi!
Jiang Ming.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
You had too much to drink last night.
I'm okay.
Do you need something from me?
You were drunk last night.
So I don't know
if you still remember
what I said.
I'm sorry.
I don't really remember...
I...
Hi, sir.
You guys go ahead.
Sorry, Sang Zhi.
I didn't know your brother was here.
It's okay.
What were you trying to say just now?
Actually,
I wanted to tell you that
on New Year's Eve.
But you didn't come that night.
Last night,
I sang a song at the bar.
Song?
For you...
Yes.
I was playing the guitar
as I sang at the bar.
Yes, you even played the guitar
and sang.
I prepared the performance for you.
For me?
I'd prepared
that song for a long time.
Thank you.
Sang Zhi,
I like you.
I want you to know that.
It's good to be appreciated by someone.
You can thank him for appreciating you
and then politely reject him.
Thank you for liking me.
I understand.
But
I'm into someone else.
So,
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
There's no need to apologize.
We're still friends
after this, right?
Of course.
Take the breakfast with you and eat it on the way.
Okay.
Thank you.
You should get in the car.
Your brother is waiting for you.
I'll get going then.
Bye-bye.
Is it delicious?
Then eat more.
After this, I have something to ask you.
We went to the bar yesterday
because we...
We had planned to have fun.
The exam was difficult, you see.
The bar was also nearby
the campus. So...
It was mostly students at the bar,
so it was not dangerous at all.
Besides, you know
I don't usually drink much.
Who did you go with?
My roommates.
I know all of them.
Roommates?
The guy
who came out with you yesterday,
1.95 meters tall,
the one who just gave you a hamburger,
is he also your roommate?
No, that's a friend
of my roommate's boyfriend.
Is that him?
What do you mean by that?
The guy you like.
Is it him?
Is he?
What's this?
The breakfast he gave me.
Is this a beef burger?
You can't eat this.
I'll take it.
I'm sorry, Jiaxu.
I threw up on you,
right?
I wasn't dreaming, right?
Are you really
that hungry?
No.
Why don't you
give me
the clothes I dirtied?
I'll give them back to you after I clean them.
You drank quite a lot last night.
It's okay.
I know you drank too much,
and you're not feeling well today.
So have some fruit.
I'll buy you something hot to drink
when we get to the airport.
Thank you.
Okay, we're leaving now.
♪My universe is hidden somewhere♪
♪No one can figure out with the glass in between♪
♪Which planet♪
♪Your name is engraved on♪
♪I'm like a balloon
that is quietly getting lighter♪
♪My worries are running away from my mind♪
♪Silently floating around you♪
♪As I get closer to you♪
♪A lime-scented breeze blows♪
♪My fingertips♪
♪Pass by your cuffs♪
♪Completing a secret love tour♪
♪Could I look at you one more time?♪
♪Let my heartbeat have one more second♪
♪It's so strange that my gaze♪
♪Always follows you around♪
♪Could I think of you one more time?♪
♪Feeling the unstoppable excitement♪
♪Like the first snow waiting for a clear sky♪
♪I've been waiting for your appearance♪